upcitemdb.com 2019-04-25

# Privacy Policy - UPCitemdb

Last updated: May 28, 2018 

The policies below are applicable to (a) the Site (www.upcitemdb.com); (b) the API service under available sub-domains owned and operated by upcitemdb.com (collectively, "we", "us", "Our" or "UPCitemdb"). 

**Information Collected Directly from You**

Information to Contact You: We collect information that is provided by you as it relates to the Site, API service. The information you provide may include a mix of personal and non-personal or non-sensitive information, such as your name, title, company name and URL, address, phone number, email address, and other relevant data that pertains to the subject matter. The information we collect is used by us to perform the requests made by you, or to contact you in regards to our Site or API service, or your general reason for inquiry.  
Creating Your Account: When you create an account to access the API subscription service, we may collect your username, email address, organization name, password. If you choose to register by using a third-party account, we may collect your information or data from such third parties if you give permission to those third parties to share your information with upcitemdb.com. There are certain information that we collect from you or store on an ongoing basis while your account is active, such as the user information, query statistics, that is relevant to support and continue the service you are receiving from us. You don't need to create an account or sign in by using a third-party account to use the Site or get trial access to the API service.  
Credit Card Information: When subscribing any paid API service plan with a credit card, we may require you to provide us with your credit card billing information, such as name, address, and a valid credit card number, to collect a recurring monthly subscription fee from you. To process the payment with your credit card, the credit card billing information is collected, stored, and processed by a third-party payment processor, [Stripe](https://stripe.com/us/privacy/), for the sole purpose of credit card processing on UPCitemdb's behalf. 

**Information Collected Indirectly about You**

Use of Cookies: upcitemdb.com uses tracking services that employ cookies to make your interactions with the Site easy and meaningful. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. The use of cookies helps us to compile aggregate data about traffic, interactions, or other statistics on the Site, and to improve the Site and user experience. The information gathered may include your domain name, computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, your searches or pages of the Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit to the Site, the time spent on the Site, your location, your Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, your operating system, and other statistics. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. This is done through your browser setting, and each browser is different, so please refer at your browser's Help menu to learn how to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies as off, it will not affect your experience with the Site. But you can not login to your account if you created one.  
Website Analytics: We use [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy) to assist us with web analytics, such as evaluating the use and operation of our Site, so that we can continue to enhance the Site and service. Please note upcitemdb.com does not have any access or control of third-party cookies, including session ID cookies, and we highly advise that you refer to the third-party's privacy policy for further information on your privacy rights.  
Log Files: As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.  
We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. Or We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services, analytics, or site functionality.  
Third Party Advertising: Some of the ads appearing on the Site are delivered to users by Google, LinkShare, Commision Junction, eBay and other web advertising partners. These third party advertising partners collect information about users' visits to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), and use that information to serve ads to users on this site, other websites, and other forms of media. Any tracking done by Web advertising partners through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to their own privacy policies. 

**Use of Information Collected**

UPCitemdb is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site and other availabe sub-domains. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that varies from what is disclosed in this statement. upcitemdb.com collects information from our users at several different areas on our site.  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you service. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Data Location and Security**

UPCitemdb uses [Red Hat](https://www.redhat.com/en/about/privacy-policy) API Management to manage API user accounts, so your account information is collected, stored and processed by Red Hat 3scale API Management Platform. We limit access to your account data only to API support employees. 

**Do Not Track**

UPCitemdb does not track its customers over time and across third-party websites, and therefore does not respond to the Do Not Track (DNT) signals. Please note that some third-party websites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve the ads content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. 

**Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)**

The Federal Trade Commission enforces COPPA, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online. Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. The Site is a general audience site not directed to children under the age of 13, and the Company does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining parental consent. 

**Outbound Links**

The Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that UPCitemdb is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each other site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

UPCitemdb reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial or bankruptcy proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Site. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request and to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

**Notice for California Users**

Under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, California consumers are entitled to the following specific consumer rights notice: The Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs may be contacted in writing at 1625 N. Market Blvd., Suite S-202, Sacramento, California 95834, or by telephone at (800) 952-5210. 

**Contact Us**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, or about the Site, please email to privacy @upcitemdb.com or mail to 530 Showers Dr. Ste 7-406, Mountain View, CA 94040.
